# Divyarajsingh Mandale Software Engineer

## **Executive Summary**

Skilled DevOps Engineer with hands-on experience of 2+ yr in supporting, automating, and optimizing mission deployments in AWS, and DevOps processes.

Experience in DevOps Tools such as Version Control - Git, Github, Build Tool - Maven, Web Application Server- Tomcat, Continuous Integration Tool - Jenkins, Containerization Tool - Docker, Container Orchestration Tool - Kubernetes (Basic), Configuration Management Tool - Ansible.

### **Professional Experience**

Company: GlobalLogic India, GlobalLogic India Limited - Nagpur SEZ Nagpur MIHAN, SEZ MH India

Duration: Jun 2022 - Present (over 1 year)

Role: Software Engineer

Project Description: BookMYSlot project helps to book the slot and make the process automated.

Responsibilities: 1. Performing both manual and automation builds using Maven and Jenkins for projects.

- 2. Implemented AWS solutions using VPC, EC2, S3, RDS, IAM, Elastic Load Balancer, Auto-scaling, and Security groups.
- 3. Experienced in managing infrastructure as a code using Terraform.
- 4. Created Docker files and build images and push to the Docker private registry.
- 5.Installing, configuring and administering Jenkins CI/CD tool and Created CI/CD pipelines.
- 6. Worked on creation of custom Docker container images, tagging and pushing the images.
- 7. Hands on experience on writing Jenkins to automate CI and CD.
- 8. Created playbook for installing packages on worker machine using ansible.

Technologies: Jenkins, Terraform, Ansible, Docker, Kubernets, Git, Maven, AWS.

Company: Mativel Solutions, Bangalore

Duration: Feb 2021 - Jul 2022 (over 1 year)

Role: Developer

**Project Description:** Vendue is a software used to manage interaction with customer. The aim of a Vendue is to allow businesses to better manage their customer relationships and ultimately drive more success.

Responsibilities: 1. Implementing various development, testing, automation tools, and IT infrastructure.

- 2. Software Configuration management (Automate CI/CD pipe using Jenkins, Maven,& GIT).
- 3. Responsible for tagging and maintain code on version control GIT.
- 4. Perform Build activities using Maven and Jenkins tool.
- 5. Configured Jenkins Jobs, install plugins for generating Project artifacts.
- 6. Automate the build Process Using Jenkins jobs.
- 7. Perform Deployment of War files in Tomcat application servers.
- 8. Responsible to write Docker files to build docker images and containers and maintain docker private repository.

Technologies: Git, GitHub, Maven, Jenkins, Terraform, Tomcat, Docker.

#### **Education**

Institution: Priyadarshini college of engineering

Dates Attended: July 2014 - June 2018Qualification(s): Bachelor Of Engineering

Major Subject(s): Design, Quality

# GlobalLogic<sup>®</sup>

A Hitachi Group Company

Central Facility Building, 2nd Floor - Wing "A" North & South and Wing "B" North & South side Block, Near Khapri Railway, MIHAN SEZ, Nagpur - 440034, India

Phone: +91-7104-669600 | www.globallogic.com

### Foreign Language Skills

Language	Written	Spoken
English	Advanced	Advanced
Hindi	Advanced	Advanced
Marathi	Advanced	Advanced

### **Technical Skills**

Skill	Skill Sub Category	
DevOps	Amazon AWS, Jenkins, Docker, Kubernetes, Terraform, Ansible	
Configuration Management	Git, GitHub	